Guide to The Alfred C. Berol Collection of Lewis Carroll 1845-1993 MSS.057
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 4: Photographs, 109045
  - Subseries 4A: Photographs by Charles L. Dodgson., 109056
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Brook and Hugh Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2336, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length. On verso numbered "2336". 4 x 2.5, undated; 1986; 109103 (Box 7, Folder 566)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Liddell, Alice, Edith and Lorina Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2463, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Sir W.B. Richmond"s painting of Liddell girls at the beach. 2463 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1989; 109102 (Box 7, Folder 567)
    - [Dodgson, Charles ] Photo of Liddon, Rev. H.P Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Seated, reading. Signed on verso "Miss E [T] Sewell/from the artist 4 x 2.5, undated; 1990; 109101 (Box 7, Folder 568)
    - [Dodgson, Charles ] Photo of Ruskin, John Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2309, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Seated in chair. Numbered "2309" Signed on verso "Miss Effie Neef /From the Artist/Nov. 11,"79. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1993; 109100 (Box 7, Folder 569)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Standen, Isabel Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 1813, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] With croquet mallet. Numbered on verso "1813" and "VIII 126". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1996; 109099 (Box 7, Folder 570)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Standen, Maud and Isabel Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 1812, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] With brick wall and foliage. Numbered "1812" and "VIII 126". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1999; 109098 (Box 7, Folder 571)
    - [Dodgson, Charles] Photo of Stevens, Enid or Winifred Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Seated on chair. See XII 220 in correspondence. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2002; 109097 (Box 7, Folder 572)
    - [Dodgson, Charles] Photo of Stevens, Enid or Winifred Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Seated on bench. On verso "W. Forshaw/Platinotype/Portraits/ Oxford/ 57 Giles". See XII 220) 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2005; 109096 (Box 7, Folder 573)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Charles Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Full length figure with croquet mallet standing before brick wall. 4 x 3, undated; 2008; 109095 (Box 8, Folder 574)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Charles Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length seated figure wearing suit with vertical stripes. 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2009; 109094 (Box 8, Folder 575)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Ellen Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Full length figure dressed in kimono standing in front of cloth backdrop and brick wall. 8.25 x 6.5, undated; 2010; 109093 (Box 8, Folder 576)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 1343, Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Girl in dress leans against prop. 8x10"Numbered "1343" on verso. Not mounted on pasteboard. 10 x 7.75, undated; 2011; 109092 (Box 8, Folder 577)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number, Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Girl sits on rug in front of prop. No number. 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2014; 109091 (Box 8, Folder 578)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Girl sits on rug in front of prop. No number. 6.25 x 4.75, undated; 2015; 109090 (Box 8, Folder 579)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure with head averted and eyes closed standing against brick wall. 4 x 3, undated; 2019; 109089 (Box 8, Folder 580)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Girl pares fruit with one foot up on box. 8x10. 9.75 x 7.75, undated; 2020; 109088 (Box 8, Folder 581)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] Full length figure with head averted standing against door. 4 x 3, undated; 2021; 109087 (Box 8, Folder 582)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n], Not Mounted [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure with eyes closed leaning against a door background of door and brick wall, with head reflected in glass panel of door. 4 x 3, undated; 2022; 109086 (Box 8, Folder 583)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure seated with ends of scarf crossing on her chest 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2023; 109085 (Box 8, Folder 584)
    - Dodgson, Charles Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure in checked skirt, double puffed sleeves, and doublet with embroidered edge. 4 x 3, undated; 2024; 109084 (Box 8, Folder 585)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure of woman in flowered print dress and beribboned cap reclining in an easy chair. 8.25 x 6.25, undated; 2025; 109083 (Box 8, Folder 586)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Full side view of Terry, Kate as Andromeda with crossed arms suspended from a silken rope. 9.75 x 7.75, undated; 2026; 109082 (Box 8, Folder 587)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Full length figure in chain mail with hand clasping a sword, and with a background of a prop supported by a brick wall. 8.5 x 6.5, undated; 2027; 109081 (Box 8, Folder 588)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Sarah and Benjamin Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[1342] [n.p.][n.d.] 2 full length figures, one seated other standing. Against a cloth backdrop. 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2028; 109080 (Box 8, Folder 589)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence and [Kate] Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 2 full length figures one seated, one leaning over other to read text in lap. Both in doorway. 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2029; 109079 (Box 8, Folder 590)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Marion Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Two full length figures, seated on striped knit blanket and embracing) 5.75 x 4.5, undated; 2030; 109078 (Box 8, Folder 591)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Ellen and Kate Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2372 [n.p.][n.d.] Ellen confers knighthood on Kate. Numbered "2372" on verso. Not mounted on pasteboard. 8.25 x 6.75, undated; 2031; 109077 (Box 8, Folder 592)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Ellen and Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number 2372 [n.p.][n.d.] Ellen confers knighthood on Kate. Numbered "2372" on verso. Not mounted on pasteboard. 8.25 x 6.25, undated; 2032; 109076 (Box 8, Folder 593)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Sarah and Kate Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 2 3/4 length figures, one leaning over the shoulder of other reading book. 6.5 x 4.75, undated; 2033; 109075 (Box 8, Folder 594)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Sarah and Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 2 3/4 length figures, one leaning over the shoulder of other reading book. 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2034; 109074 (Box 8, Folder 595)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry Family Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] Kentish Town, July 15, 1865 At the family"s home in Kentish Town on July 15th, 1865. Not Mounted on Pasteboard. 7.75 x 9.75, 2041; 109073 (Box 8, Folder 596)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Croft Rectory, Yorkshire, before 1868 Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 1. 3 x 4, undated; 2042; 109072 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Croft Church, Yorkshire Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 2. 2.25 x 3.5, undated; 2043; 109071 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Croft Churchyard Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 3. 2.75 x 4, undated; 2044; 109070 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Croft Churchyard Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 4. 2.75 x 3.75, undated; 2045; 109069 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Interior of Croft Church Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 5. 3 x 3.75, undated; 2046; 109068 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of The Study of Croft Rectory Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 6 3.5 x 2.75, undated; 2047; 109067 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of The Drawing Room of Croft Rectory Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 7. 3 x 4, undated; 2048; 109066 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of National School, Croft Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 8. 3 x 3.75, undated; 2049; 109065 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Unidentified photo Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 8 verso, Photo Album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks. 2.75 x 3.75, undated; 2050; 109064 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Unidentified photo Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 9. 3.5 x 3.75, undated; 2051; 109063 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Unidentified photo Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 9. 2.25 x 3.5, undated; 2052; 109062 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - [Dodgson, Charles] [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Agnes Mary Collingwood Grave Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 10. 4 x 5.75, undated; 2053; 109061 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Unknown [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Croft Church Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 11. 6 x 8.5, undated; 2054; 109060 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Unknown [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Interior of Croft Church Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 12 6 x 8.5, undated; 2055; 109059 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Girl Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2224 [n.p.][n.d.] Holding tambourine. Wearing costume and jewelry. Numbered "2224" on verso. 5 x 3.5, undated; 2056; 109058 (Box 8, Folder 598)
    - Charles Dodgson Unknown Contemporary Glass Photographic Plate, Negative Number 751 [n.p.][n.d.]. 12 x 10, undated; 2057; 109057 (Box 8, Folder 599)
  - Subseries 4B: Photographs by others, 109046
    - Marks, Barbara S. Stone Rabbit at St. Mary"s Church, Yorkshire Modern Photographic Print, [n.p.][n.d.]., undated; 109055 (Box 8, Folder 600)
    - Unknown Photo of Dodgson, Charles Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Numbered "28" on verso, inscribed "M.S, Cunnynghame/ from Lewis Carroll", also numbered II 37 in red pencil. Mounted on pasteboard. 4 x 2.5, undated; 2058; 109054 (Box 8, Folder 601)
    - Unknown Photo of Dodgson, Charles Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Mounted on pasteboard. Inscribed on verso in print at top " to LC from LC." and below in script "for Lizzie Coote/ from CLD/ Mar. 28 1876" and below in a different hand "Author of Alice/in Wonderland.." Mounted on pasteboard. 4 x 2.5, undated; 2061; 109053 (Box 8, Folder 602)
    - Unknown Photo of Dodgson, Charles Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n.] [n.p.][n.d.] Mounted on pasteboard. Inscribed on verso in script. At top "CLD" followed by partial numeral beginning "22.." below " Lizzie Coote/ from CLD/ with love /May 1. /78,". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2064; 109052 (Box 8, Folder 603)
    - Unknown Photo of Dodgson, Charles Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n.] [n.p.][n.d.] In glass. Inscribed on verso "Lucy Wilcox/ from her afftc Cousin/ the Substance, whose/ actinic image is/ on the other side./ June 10 /78" 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2067; 109051 (Box 8, Folder 604)
    - Unknown Photo of Dodgson, Charles Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n.] [n.p.][n.d.] Funeral Card. In folding pasteboard case labeled "In Memoriam" on front, inscribed in pencil on back "From L. Dodgson". 5 x 3, undated; 2070; 109050 (Box 8, Folder 605)
    - Unknown Photograph of Ellen Terry Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n.] [n.p.][n.d.] Matted., undated; 109049 (Box 8, Folder 606)
    - Unknown Photo of Saville Clarkes Dream Play, "Twinkle, Twinkle Little Bat" Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n.] Photo includes Phoebe Carlo. [n.p.][n.d.]. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2071; 109048 (Box 8, Folder 607)
    - Unknown Photo of Saville Clarkes Dream Play, "I Used to be a Real Turtle" Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n.] [n.p.][n.d.]. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2072; 109047 (Box 8, Folder 608)
  - Subseries 4C: Photographs and Negatives File (Box 22)
- Series 5: Related Materials., 108987
  - Subseries 5A: Advertisements., 109042
    - Courtland"s Department Store Display Magazine., undated; 109044 (Box 9, Folder 610)
    - International Paper "They"ll Live Forever Through Print and Paper"., undated; 109043 (Box 9, Folder 611)
  - Subseries 5B: Articles on Dodgson and/or his works., 109023
    - Abeles, Francine "Ranking by Inversion: A Note on C.L. Dodgson" "Determinants and Linear Systems: Charles L. Dodgson"s View" "C.L. Dodgson and Apportionment for Proportional Representation" "Power in Decisions Amongst Multiple Alternatives" "Multiplication in Changing Bases: A Note on Lewis Carroll" Other Miscellaneous articles, undated; 109041 (Box 9, Folder 612)
    - Ayers, Harry Morgan Lewis Carroll"s Withdrawal of the 1865 Alice., undated; 109040 (Box 9, Folder 613)
    - Batey, Mavis Alices Adventures in Oxford., undated; 109039 (Box 9, Folder 614)
    - Black, Duncan "Lewis Carroll and the Cambridge Mathematical School"., undated; 109038 (Box 9, Folder 615)
    - Bond, W.H. "The Publication of Alice"s Adventures"., undated; 109037 (Box 9, Folder 616)
    - Goodacre, Selwyn "The Listing of the Snark"., undated; 109036 (Box 9, Folder 617)
    - Hancock, Cecily Raysor "Musical Notes to the Annotated Alice"., undated; 109035 (Box 9, Folder 618)
    - Jackson, Joseph Alice as a Book and a Treasure., undated; 109034 (Box 9, Folder 619)
    - Squire, J.C. Speech at the Opening Ceremony., undated; 109033 (Box 9, Folder 620)
    - Stafford, Jean "The Jabberwock Anatomized" in The Griffin., undated; 109032 (Box 9, Folder 621)
    - Swan, Bradford F. Auctioning Alice., undated; 109031 (Box 9, Folder 622)
    - Vail, R.W.G. Alice in Wonderland :The Manuscript and its Story., undated; 109030 (Box 9, Folder 623)
    - Van Patten, Nathan The Yerba Buena Press and Some Related Privately Printed Books., undated; 109029 (Box 9, Folder 624)
    - Warde, B.L. Printing Should Be Invisible., undated; 109028 (Box 9, Folder 625)
    - Weaver, Warren The India Alice With corrected Ms., proofs, and letters., undated; 109027 (Box 9, Folder 626)
    - Weaver, Warren Lewis Carroll and a Geometrical Paradox., undated; 109026 (Box 9, Folder 627)
    - Weaver, Warren Lewis Carroll Correspondence Numbers With corrected Ms., proofs, and letters, undated; 109025 (Box 9, Folder 628)
    - Weaver, Warren "Lewis Carroll Mathemetician"., undated; 109024 (Box 9, Folder 629)
  - Subseries 5C:Ephemera., 109005
    - Arcadia Works, London 48 Playing Cards, 2 .5" by 3". In case., undated; 109022 (Box 9, Folder 630)
    - Arcadia Works, London 48 Playing Cards, 2 .5" by 3". Loose Deck #2., undated; 109021 (Box 9, Folder 631)
    - Arcadia Works, London 48 Playing Cards, 2 .5" by 3", Loose Deck #3., undated; 109020 (Box 9, Folder 632)
    - Arcadia Works, London 1 Set Playing Cards, 1 .5" by 2 .75". Loose miniature., undated; 109019 (Box 9, Folder 633)
    - Dodgson, Charles L. Jabberwocky in Punch Photocopy., undated; 109018 (Box 10, Folder 634)
    - Dodgson, Charles L. Wonderland Postage Stamp Cases(4), undated; 109017 (Box 10, Folder 635)
    - Hatch, Ethel Watercolor Untitled [n.p.], [n.d.]., undated; 109016 (Box 10, Folder 636)
    - Wildridge, T. Tindall "A Lewis Carroll Pageant" Four of a series of six, undated; 109015 (Box 10, Folder 637)
    - Unknown Christmas Cards Using Alice, undated; 109014 (Box 10, Folder 638)
    - Unknown Doily [The Walrus and the Carpenter]., undated; 109013 (Box 10, Folder 639)
    - Unknown Ivory Hatter., undated; 109012 (Box 10, Folder 640)
    - Unknown The Postage Stamps of Wonderland., undated; 109011 (Box 10, Folder 641)
    - Unknown Stereoscopic Cards., undated; 109010 (Box 10, Folder 642)
    - Unknown The Tuck Alice 1926., undated; 109009 (Box 10, Folder 643)
    - Unknown Gold Watch Marked on back of works "examined by A.S. Bach, 40, Great Russel St., London W.C." Inscribed on inside "Menella from C.L.D. 1888"., undated; 109008 (Box 10, Folder Vault)
    - Unknown Wonderland postage stamps affixed to Envelopes., undated; 109007 (Box 10, Folder 644)
    - Various Material on NY Central Park Memorial., undated; 109006 (Box 10, Folder 645)
  - Subseries 5D: Magazines with Articles on Dodgson and/or his works., 109004
  - Subseries 5E: Newspaper Clippings., 109001
    - Contemporary Newspaper Clippings Obituaries of Dodgson, Charles., undated; 109003 (Box 10, Folder 646)
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings., undated; 109002 (Box 10, Folder 647)
  - Subseries 5F: Reprints of Dodgson., 108996
    - Dodgson, Charles Address by the Rev. C.L. Dodgson at St. Mary Magdelene Church, St. Leonards-on-Sea., undated; 109000 (Box 10, Folder 648)
    - Dodgson, Charles Arithmetical Puzzle By Lewis Carroll., undated; 108999 (Box 10, Folder 649)
    - Dodgson, Charles How the Boots Got Left Behind., undated; 108998 (Box 10, Folder 650)
    - Dodgson, Charles The Three Cats., undated; 108997 (Box 10, Folder 651)
  - Subseries 5G: Theater Materials., 108988
    - Henry Savile-Clarke Alice in Wonderland: A Dream Play for Children., undated; 108995 (Box 10, Folder 652)
    - Miscellaneous Kitty Saville-Clarke Materials 4 Letters and a Performance copy of Henry Saville Clarke"s The Phantom Cutlet., undated; 108994 (Box 10, Folder 653)
    - Theater Program (photocopy) Alice"s Adventures in Wonderland Daniel Press Original in Daniel Press boxes., undated; 108993 (Box 10, Folder 654)
    - Theater Programs Eva Le Gallienne Productions "Alice in Wonderland" (1931, 1947, 1982), 1931-1982; 108992 (Box 10, Folder 655)
    - Theater Program National Ballet of Canada "Alice"(1986), 108991 (Box 10, Folder 656)
    - Theater Program O"Neill, Randall "Alice in Wonderland"(1931), 108990 (Box 10, Folder 657)
    - Theater Program Princeton University Players (1954) Princeton University Triangle Club (1953), 108989 (Box 10, Folder 658)
- Series 6: Provenance, 108850
  - Subseries 6A: Checklists., 108985
    - Checklists of the Berol Collection., undated; 108986 (Box 11, Folder 659)
  - Subseries 6B:Typescripts., 108982
    - Typescript Dodgson Letters., undated; 108984 (Box 11, Folder 660)
    - Typescript Dodgson Letters II., undated; 108983 (Box 11, Folder 661)
  - Subseries 6C1: Correspondence Regarding Collection Materials. (Collection Development and Alfred C. Berol.), 108968
    - Berol Correspondence (multiple letters), undated; 108981 (Box 11, Folder 662)
    - AB Sandbergs Bohandel to Berol, Alfred., undated; 108980 (Box 11, Folder ID: 662.1)
    - Bond, W.H. to Berol, Alfred., undated; 108979 (Box 11, Folder ID: 662.2)
    - Dodgson, F. Menella to Berol, Alfred and Kenneth Berol., undated; 108978 (Box 11, Folder 663)
    - Drake, M. to Berol, Alfred., undated; 108977 (Box 11, Folder ID: 663.1)
    - Gibb, Jocelyn to Berol, Alfred., undated; 108976 (Box 11, Folder ID: 663.2)
    - Gielgud, John / Berol, Afred Correspondence., undated; 108975 (Box 11, Folder 664)
    - Goldsmith, Alfred to Berol, Alfred., undated; 108974 (Box 11, Folder 665)
    - Hudson, Derek to Berol, Alfred 666.1 Jackson, [?] to Berol, Alfred., undated; 108973 (Box 11, Folder 666)
    - Livingston, F. to Berol, Alfred., undated; 108972 (Box 11, Folder ID: 666.2)
    - Mason, J.F.A. to Berol, Alfred., undated; 108971 (Box 11, Folder ID: 666.3)
    - Quaritch, Bernard to Berol, Alfred., undated; 108970 (Box 11, Folder 667)
    - Wright, C.P. to Berol Alfred (w/ reply)., undated; 108969 (Box 11, Folder ID: 667.1)
  - Subseries 6C2: Correspondence Regarding Collection Materials. (Collection Development and Others)., 108958
    - Carter, John misc. Correspondence., undated; 108967 (Box 11, Folder 668)
    - Clevedon, Douglas to Harrmsworth R.L. (2)., undated; 108966 (Box 11, Folder ID: 668.1)
    - Collingwood, Grace J., to Messrs Maggs Brothers., undated; 108965 (Box 11, Folder 669)
    - Fordham, Hallam to Gielgud, Mrs. Kate Terry., undated; 108964 (Box 11, Folder 670)
    - Madan, Falconer to Strong, H., undated; 108963 (Box 11, Folder ID: 670.1)
    - Parish and Company to Harmsworth, Sir Leicester., undated; 108962 (Box 11, Folder 671)
    - Watson, H.D.to Hatch, Evelyn., undated; 108961 (Box 11, Folder ID: 671.1)
    - Weaver, Warren misc. Correspondence., undated; 108960 (Box 11, Folder 672)
    - Williams, Sidney to Forman., undated; 108959 (Box 11, Folder ID: 672.1)
  - Subseries 6D: Provenance Notes, 108896
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Duchess of Albany., undated; 108957 (Box 11, Folder 673)